威尔 · 森坦斯: 但是还有一点。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But
there's one more bit.
如果我们正如彼得所说,
If we're filling in, as Peter says,
用来自 Twitter 的数据，字符串 hi,
that value property with
the data from Twitter, string hi,
然后我们希望能够以某种方式使用它，展示它，利用它。
then we wanna be able to use that in
some way, display it, make use of it.
马克，你能帮帮我吗？
Mark, can you help me out?
如果我知道值属性更新时,
If I know that when that
value property gets updated,
它会自动运行这个未完成数组中的任何函数。
it's going to automatically run any
function in this unfulfilled array.
如何将函数添加到这个隐藏的未实现数组中？
How do I get a function into
this hidden unfulfilled array?
我应该用什么方法把一个函数放到这个未完成的数组中，马克？
What method am I given to get a function
into that unfulfilled array, Mark?
离开银幕。 那么，威尔 · 森坦斯: 。 然后是 then 方法。
&gt;&gt; off-screen male: .then
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: .then, the then method.
完全正确。
Exactly right.
它的承诺是由 JavaScript 设计的自动触发
The promise of it is designed by
JavaScript to automatically trigger
以此值作为输入运行该数组中的函数
the functions in this array to
run with this value as its input
当这个值被 JavaScript 自动更新的时候。
when that value gets updated
automatically by JavaScript, okay.
现在我们来做这个附件。
So let's do that attachment right now.
然后，我们传入整个引用,
FutureData.then, we pass
in the entire reference,
我们会连接到整个显示功能。
we'll link to the entire display function.
这就是整个显示功能。
There it is, the entire display function.
我们要把它抓起来放进去，我要在这里吸一口吗？
We're gonna grab it and store it into,
should I do a line here?
然后抓起来放进去，我知道该怎么做了。
And grab it and store it into,
I know what I'll do.
然后把它存储进去，所以未来的数据就是这个粉红色的物体。
Gonna grab it and store it into, so
future data is this pink object here.
我们要抓取它，并将其存储到未实现的数组中，在那个承诺对象中。
We're gonna grab it and store it into
array unfulfilled, in that promise object.
所以我们要抓住显示器和[声音]使用声音效果，对不对？
So we're gonna grab display and
[SOUND] using sound effects, right?
进入未完成的数组，它就在那里。
In it goes into the unfulfilled array,
there it is.
显示功能。
The display function.
这意味着当后台工作完成后,
So that means that when
the background work completes,
value 属性会更新，它会自动触发显示
the value property gets updated,
it's automatically gonna trigger display
运行，其中显示的输入被返回或
to run, where display's
input being the returned or
响应对象就是 Tweet，字符串 hi。
the response object which is gonna
be just that Tweet, the string hi.
看起来它会被展示出来,
And it's gonna fill in by
the looks of it into display,
他们已经准备好了一些参数。
they've got a little parameter waiting.
数据可以用字符串 hi，参数填充。
Data can be filled in with the string hi,
the argument.
非常好。
Very nice.
[声音]很好，我们已经准备好了两个背景作品。
[SOUND] Good, we have set up
two pieces of background work.
其中一个已经完成并且在队列中，相关的函数,
One of them's already complete and landed
in the queue, the associated function,
准备跑。
ready to run.
我肯定它随时都会播出。
I'm sure it's gonna run any moment now.
当我们接近2毫秒的时候,
As we head on to at 2 milliseconds,
我们要执行什么功能？
we're going to execute what function?
Jason 在2毫秒的时间里我们刚刚完成了未来,
Jason, at 2 milliseconds,
we just finished our FutureDays.then,
我们要在2毫秒内运行什么函数，杰森？
we're gonna run what function
at 2 milliseconds, Jason?
我们将进行显示或假设我们在下面一行,
&gt;&gt; off-screen male: We are going to run
display or assuming we're one line below,
blockfor300ms.
BlockFor300ms.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 阻塞300毫秒，他说对了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: BlockFor300ms,
he's spot on.
就是这个，BlockFor300ms。
There it is, BlockFor300ms.
全新的。
Brand new.
[笑声]演讲者3: 执行环境。
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Execution context.
威尔 · 森特斯: 美丽的人，没错！
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful people,
exactly!
运行 BlockFor300ms 的全新执行环境。
Brand new execution context for
running BlockFor300ms.
我们的电话记录我们要通过人员,
It's going on our call stack,
we're gonna go through people,
很快就能抹去它了。
it's gonna fun to erase it in a moment.
300毫秒，我们进入它。
BlockFor300ms, into it we go.
然后，我们开始，它会增加300毫秒，但是你不会相信。
And, in we go, it's gonna add 300
milliseconds, but you won't believe it.
当我们在里面的时候，你不会相信这里发生了什么。
While we're inside there,
you won't believe what happens down here.
好消息。
Good news people.
Good news.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们亲爱的推特朋友骑马回来了
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Our dear friend
from Twitter has come riding back and
大约在270毫秒的时候说，嘿，我有微博。
said at roughly 270 milliseconds,
hey, I've got tweets.
我得到了 tweets，在270毫秒的时间里，它就完成了。
I've got tweets and at 270 milliseconds,
there it is, it's complete.
我们带回了什么？
And what do we bring back?
我们的推特是什么，彼得？
What's our tweet, Peter?
屏幕外的男性: 字符串 hi。
&gt;&gt; off-screen male: The string hi.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 当然是这根绳子了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The string hi,
of course it is.
就是这个，绳子 hi。
There it is, the string hi.
好了，现在，事情变得有趣了。
Okay, now, stuff gets interesting.
当他回来或者从互联网上得到回复时,
When hi returns or gets responded
back from speaking to the Internet,
马克，什么自己的完成会发生？
Mark, what own completion is gonna happen?
屏幕外雄: FutureData.value。
&gt;&gt; off-screen male: FutureData.value.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这将是[相声]精确的,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's gonna
be [CROSSTALK] exactly,
会触发 Kayla 在调用堆栈上运行什么函数？
which is gonna trigger, Kayla,
what function to run on the call stack?
没有。
No.
屏幕外的女性: 不，在排队。
&gt;&gt; off-screen female: No, on the queue.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这听起来非常合理，这肯定是一个迹象。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's sounds eminently
reasonable, which is surely a sign.
(笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们确定的是
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What we're sure is that
它不会直接进入调用堆栈，不可能。
it doesn't go straight on the call stack,
no way.
这是不可能的，对吧，因为我们有300毫秒的阻塞。
There's no way it can, right, because
we've got BlockFor300ms right there.
我们现在大概是，会是多少？
We're right now at roughly,
what would it be?
我们大概在，我不知道，这里是什么，270毫秒，或者
We're at roughly, I don't know,
what is it, 270 milliseconds in here, or
周围的东西。
something around.
这就是我们现在所处的情况。
That's at the point that
we're in right now.
等等，我们不能突然在调用堆栈上显示。
Hold on, we can't suddenly throw
display on the call stack.
所以现在，我们注意到，是的，没错。
So let's for now,
let's note, yes, exactly.
然后进入回调队列。
On to the callback queue it goes.
我肯定那是正确的。
I'm sure that must be correct.
这听起来很合逻辑。
That sounds very logical.
这相当于270毫秒。
And that's like 270 milliseconds.
好的，BlockFor300ms 继续运行。
Okay, BlockFor300ms continues running.
我们退出，大家会怎么想,
We exit out, and
what would that be everybody,
大概是302毫秒。
302 milliseconds, yeah, roughly.
可能，确切地说，大致地说，不管怎样。
Probably, exactly, roughly, whatever.
302毫秒，我们把这个从调用堆栈上取下来。
302 milliseconds,
let's get this off the call stack.
让我们从调用堆栈中获取 BlockFor300ms。
Let's get BlockFor300ms
off the call stack.
顺便说一句目前为止大家都很好,
By the way everybody, all so good so far,
在302毫秒的时间里，没有我们没见过的东西。
nothing we haven't seen
before at 302 milliseconds.
已经坐在那里等了302毫秒。
printHello has been sitting there
waiting for literally 302 milliseconds.
我想现在它可以跑了，对吧？
I assume now it's allowed to run, right?
男性: 没有。
&gt;&gt; off-screen male: No.
威尔 · 桑特斯: 没有？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No?
这太疯狂了，现在该怎么办，布雷登？
This is insane, so
what's gonna run at this point, Brayden?
屏幕外男: 我先来，在显示器上。
&gt;&gt; off-screen male: The me first,
on the display.
威尔 · 森坦斯(笑) : 我看到了大脑
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I see brain
现在敏感了。
sensitization now.
在这一点上，控制台肯定会首先记录我的日志，是的，绝对会。
Definitely the console is gonna log me
first at this point, yeah, absolutely.
因此，我们首先知道，我们的异步代码将获得优先权。
So the me first., we know that our
asynchronous code is gonna get priority.
我们可以做一百万件这样的事情，总是优先处理。
We could do a million of those,
always priority.
所以在302毫秒，我们先得到我。
So at 302 milliseconds, we get me first.
就是这样，对，三百零二毫秒,
That is it, right, at 302 milliseconds,
我们得到了 console.log (我先!)。
we get console.log(Me first!).
现在，事情变得有趣了。
Now, things get interesting.